{
  "version": "1.0",
  "exportDate": "2026-12-18T00:00:00.000Z",
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "Espa침ol B1",
      "icon": "游쀯릖",
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "lograr",
          "back": "achieve"
        },
        {
          "front": "admitir",
          "back": "admit"
        },
        {
          "front": "aconsejar",
          "back": "advise"
        },
        {
          "front": "permitirse",
          "back": "afford"
        },
        {
          "front": "estar de acuerdo",
          "back": "agree"
        },
        {
          "front": "permitir",
          "back": "allow"
        },
        {
          "front": "anunciar",
          "back": "announce"
        },
        {
          "front": "disculparse",
          "back": "apologize"
        },
        {
          "front": "aparecer",
          "back": "appear"
        },
        {
          "front": "apreciar",
          "back": "appreciate"
        },
        {
          "front": "acercarse",
          "back": "approach"
        },
        {
          "front": "discutir",
          "back": "argue"
        },
        {
          "front": "arreglar",
          "back": "arrange"
        },
        {
          "front": "llegar",
          "back": "arrive"
        },
        {
          "front": "asumir",
          "back": "assume"
        },
        {
          "front": "adjuntar",
          "back": "attach"
        },
        {
          "front": "asistir",
          "back": "attend"
        },
        {
          "front": "atraer",
          "back": "attract"
        },
        {
          "front": "evitar",
          "back": "avoid"
        },
        {
          "front": "comportarse",
          "back": "behave"
        },
        {
          "front": "pertenecer",
          "back": "belong"
        },
        {
          "front": "culpar",
          "back": "blame"
        },
        {
          "front": "pedir prestado",
          "back": "borrow"
        },
        {
          "front": "respirar",
          "back": "breath"
        },
        {
          "front": "cancelar",
          "back": "cancel"
        },
        {
          "front": "cuidar",
          "back": "care"
        },
        {
          "front": "celebrar",
          "back": "celebrate"
        },
        {
          "front": "cambiar",
          "back": "change"
        },
        {
          "front": "cobrar",
          "back": "charge"
        },
        {
          "front": "perseguir",
          "back": "chase"
        },
        {
          "front": "verificar",
          "back": "check"
        },
        {
          "front": "elegir",
          "back": "choose"
        },
        {
          "front": "reclamar",
          "back": "claim"
        },
        {
          "front": "escalar",
          "back": "climb"
        },
        {
          "front": "recolectar",
          "back": "collect"
        },
        {
          "front": "combinar",
          "back": "combine"
        },
        {
          "front": "comentar",
          "back": "comment"
        },
        {
          "front": "comunicar",
          "back": "communicate"
        },
        {
          "front": "comparar",
          "back": "compare"
        },
        {
          "front": "competir",
          "back": "compete"
        },
        {
          "front": "quejarse",
          "back": "complain"
        },
        {
          "front": "completar",
          "back": "complete"
        },
        {
          "front": "concentrarse",
          "back": "concentrate"
        },
        {
          "front": "preocupar",
          "back": "concern"
        },
        {
          "front": "concluir",
          "back": "conclude"
        },
        {
          "front": "confirmar",
          "back": "confirm"
        },
        {
          "front": "conectar",
          "back": "connect"
        },
        {
          "front": "considerar",
          "back": "consider"
        },
        {
          "front": "consistir",
          "back": "consist"
        },
        {
          "front": "contener",
          "back": "contain"
        },
        {
          "front": "continuar",
          "back": "continue"
        },
        {
          "front": "contribuir",
          "back": "contribute"
        },
        {
          "front": "controlar",
          "back": "control"
        },
        {
          "front": "convencer",
          "back": "convince"
        },
        {
          "front": "copiar",
          "back": "copy"
        },
        {
          "front": "contar",
          "back": "count"
        },
        {
          "front": "cubrir",
          "back": "cover"
        },
        {
          "front": "crear",
          "back": "create"
        },
        {
          "front": "cruzar",
          "back": "cross"
        },
        {
          "front": "da침ar",
          "back": "damage"
        },
        {
          "front": "tratar",
          "back": "deal"
        },
        {
          "front": "debatir",
          "back": "debate"
        },
        {
          "front": "decidir",
          "back": "decide"
        },
        {
          "front": "defender",
          "back": "defend"
        },
        {
          "front": "retrasar",
          "back": "delay"
        },
        {
          "front": "entregar",
          "back": "deliver"
        },
        {
          "front": "exigir",
          "back": "demand"
        },
        {
          "front": "depender",
          "back": "depend"
        },
        {
          "front": "describir",
          "back": "describe"
        },
        {
          "front": "merecer",
          "back": "deserve"
        },
        {
          "front": "dise침ar",
          "back": "design"
        },
        {
          "front": "destruir",
          "back": "destroy"
        },
        {
          "front": "desarrollar",
          "back": "develop"
        },
        {
          "front": "diferir",
          "back": "differ"
        },
        {
          "front": "descubrir",
          "back": "discover"
        },
        {
          "front": "discutir",
          "back": "discuss"
        },
        {
          "front": "dividir",
          "back": "divide"
        },
        {
          "front": "dudar",
          "back": "doubt"
        },
        {
          "front": "ganar",
          "back": "earn"
        },
        {
          "front": "educar",
          "back": "educate"
        },
        {
          "front": "efecto",
          "back": "effect"
        },
        {
          "front": "esfuerzo",
          "back": "effort"
        },
        {
          "front": "alentar",
          "back": "encourage"
        },
        {
          "front": "enemigo",
          "back": "enemy"
        },
        {
          "front": "energ칤a",
          "back": "energy"
        },
        {
          "front": "comprometerse",
          "back": "engage"
        },
        {
          "front": "disfrutar",
          "back": "enjoy"
        },
        {
          "front": "asegurar",
          "back": "ensure"
        },
        {
          "front": "entrar",
          "back": "enter"
        },
        {
          "front": "medio ambiente",
          "back": "environment"
        },
        {
          "front": "igual",
          "back": "equal"
        },
        {
          "front": "equipo",
          "back": "equipment"
        },
        {
          "front": "escapar",
          "back": "escape"
        },
        {
          "front": "establecer",
          "back": "establish"
        },
        {
          "front": "estimar",
          "back": "estimate"
        },
        {
          "front": "examinar",
          "back": "examine"
        },
        {
          "front": "excepto",
          "back": "except"
        },
        {
          "front": "intercambiar",
          "back": "exchange"
        },
        {
          "front": "emocionar",
          "back": "excite"
        },
        {
          "front": "excusa",
          "back": "excuse"
        },
        {
          "front": "ejercicio",
          "back": "exercise"
        },
        {
          "front": "existir",
          "back": "exist"
        },
        {
          "front": "esperar",
          "back": "expect"
        },
        {
          "front": "experiencia",
          "back": "experience"
        },
        {
          "front": "experimento",
          "back": "experiment"
        },
        {
          "front": "explicar",
          "back": "explain"
        },
        {
          "front": "explorar",
          "back": "explore"
        },
        {
          "front": "expresar",
          "back": "express"
        },
        {
          "front": "extender",
          "back": "extend"
        },
        {
          "front": "enfrentar",
          "back": "face"
        },
        {
          "front": "fallar",
          "back": "fail"
        },
        {
          "front": "justo",
          "back": "fair"
        },
        {
          "front": "fe",
          "back": "faith"
        },
        {
          "front": "familiar",
          "back": "familiar"
        },
        {
          "front": "culpa",
          "back": "fault"
        },
        {
          "front": "favor",
          "back": "favor"
        },
        {
          "front": "miedo",
          "back": "fear"
        },
        {
          "front": "caracter칤stica",
          "back": "feature"
        },
        {
          "front": "alimentar",
          "back": "feed"
        },
        {
          "front": "luchar",
          "back": "fight"
        },
        {
          "front": "llenar",
          "back": "fill"
        },
        {
          "front": "final",
          "back": "final"
        },
        {
          "front": "arreglar",
          "back": "fix"
        },
        {
          "front": "vuelo",
          "back": "flight"
        },
        {
          "front": "fluir",
          "back": "flow"
        },
        {
          "front": "doblar",
          "back": "fold"
        },
        {
          "front": "seguir",
          "back": "follow"
        },
        {
          "front": "forzar",
          "back": "force"
        },
        {
          "front": "extranjero",
          "back": "foreign"
        },
        {
          "front": "olvidar",
          "back": "forget"
        },
        {
          "front": "perdonar",
          "back": "forgive"
        },
        {
          "front": "forma",
          "back": "form"
        },
        {
          "front": "adelante",
          "back": "forward"
        },
        {
          "front": "libertad",
          "back": "freedom"
        },
        {
          "front": "congelar",
          "back": "freeze"
        },
        {
          "front": "fresco",
          "back": "fresh"
        },
        {
          "front": "asustar",
          "back": "frighten"
        },
        {
          "front": "muebles",
          "back": "furniture"
        },
        {
          "front": "ganar",
          "back": "gain"
        },
        {
          "front": "reunir",
          "back": "gather"
        },
        {
          "front": "general",
          "back": "general"
        },
        {
          "front": "generaci칩n",
          "back": "generation"
        },
        {
          "front": "generoso",
          "back": "generous"
        },
        {
          "front": "gentil",
          "back": "gentle"
        },
        {
          "front": "meta",
          "back": "goal"
        },
        {
          "front": "agarrar",
          "back": "grab"
        },
        {
          "front": "graduarse",
          "back": "graduate"
        },
        {
          "front": "grandioso",
          "back": "grand"
        },
        {
          "front": "conceder",
          "back": "grant"
        },
        {
          "front": "agradecido",
          "back": "grateful"
        },
        {
          "front": "saludar",
          "back": "greet"
        },
        {
          "front": "suelo",
          "back": "ground"
        },
        {
          "front": "grupo",
          "back": "group"
        },
        {
          "front": "crecer",
          "back": "grow"
        },
        {
          "front": "garantizar",
          "back": "guarantee"
        },
        {
          "front": "guardia",
          "back": "guard"
        },
        {
          "front": "adivinar",
          "back": "guess"
        },
        {
          "front": "invitado",
          "back": "guest"
        },
        {
          "front": "gu칤a",
          "back": "guide"
        },
        {
          "front": "culpable",
          "back": "guilty"
        },
        {
          "front": "h치bito",
          "back": "habit"
        },
        {
          "front": "manejar",
          "back": "handle"
        },
        {
          "front": "colgar",
          "back": "hang"
        },
        {
          "front": "suceder",
          "back": "happen"
        },
        {
          "front": "da침ar",
          "back": "harm"
        },
        {
          "front": "cosecha",
          "back": "harvest"
        },
        {
          "front": "dudar",
          "back": "hesitate"
        },
        {
          "front": "esconder",
          "back": "hide"
        },
        {
          "front": "contratar",
          "back": "hire"
        },
        {
          "front": "golpear",
          "back": "hit"
        },
        {
          "front": "sostener",
          "back": "hold"
        },
        {
          "front": "honesto",
          "back": "honest"
        },
        {
          "front": "honor",
          "back": "honor"
        },
        {
          "front": "esperanza",
          "back": "hope"
        },
        {
          "front": "anfitri칩n",
          "back": "host"
        },
        {
          "front": "enorme",
          "back": "huge"
        },
        {
          "front": "humano",
          "back": "human"
        },
        {
          "front": "humilde",
          "back": "humble"
        },
        {
          "front": "humor",
          "back": "humor"
        },
        {
          "front": "cazar",
          "back": "hunt"
        },
        {
          "front": "apresurarse",
          "back": "hurry"
        },
        {
          "front": "herir",
          "back": "hurt"
        },
        {
          "front": "ignorar",
          "back": "ignore"
        },
        {
          "front": "imaginar",
          "back": "imagine"
        },
        {
          "front": "inmediato",
          "back": "immediate"
        },
        {
          "front": "impresionar",
          "back": "impress"
        },
        {
          "front": "mejorar",
          "back": "improve"
        },
        {
          "front": "incluir",
          "back": "include"
        },
        {
          "front": "ingreso",
          "back": "income"
        },
        {
          "front": "aumentar",
          "back": "increase"
        },
        {
          "front": "independiente",
          "back": "independent"
        },
        {
          "front": "indicar",
          "back": "indicate"
        },
        {
          "front": "individual",
          "back": "individual"
        },
        {
          "front": "industria",
          "back": "industry"
        },
        {
          "front": "influencia",
          "back": "influence"
        },
        {
          "front": "informar",
          "back": "inform"
        },
        {
          "front": "inicial",
          "back": "initial"
        },
        {
          "front": "lesionar",
          "back": "injure"
        },
        {
          "front": "inocente",
          "back": "innocent"
        },
        {
          "front": "insistir",
          "back": "insist"
        },
        {
          "front": "en cambio",
          "back": "instead"
        },
        {
          "front": "inteligencia",
          "back": "intelligence"
        },
        {
          "front": "intentar",
          "back": "intend"
        },
        {
          "front": "inter칠s",
          "back": "interest"
        },
        {
          "front": "interrumpir",
          "back": "interrupt"
        },
        {
          "front": "presentar",
          "back": "introduce"
        },
        {
          "front": "inventar",
          "back": "invent"
        },
        {
          "front": "invertir",
          "back": "invest"
        },
        {
          "front": "investigar",
          "back": "investigate"
        },
        {
          "front": "invitar",
          "back": "invite"
        },
        {
          "front": "involucrar",
          "back": "involve"
        },
        {
          "front": "tema",
          "back": "issue"
        },
        {
          "front": "art칤culo",
          "back": "item"
        },
        {
          "front": "celoso",
          "back": "jealous"
        },
        {
          "front": "broma",
          "back": "joke"
        },
        {
          "front": "viaje",
          "back": "journey"
        },
        {
          "front": "juzgar",
          "back": "judge"
        },
        {
          "front": "saltar",
          "back": "jump"
        },
        {
          "front": "justicia",
          "back": "justice"
        },
        {
          "front": "justificar",
          "back": "justify"
        },
        {
          "front": "entusiasta",
          "back": "keen"
        },
        {
          "front": "mantener",
          "back": "keep"
        },
        {
          "front": "clave",
          "back": "key"
        },
        {
          "front": "patear",
          "back": "kick"
        },
        {
          "front": "matar",
          "back": "kill"
        },
        {
          "front": "amable",
          "back": "kind"
        },
        {
          "front": "reino",
          "back": "kingdom"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}